Guide to the Douglas E. Hammond Collection of Computer Manuals
Douglas E. Hammond Collection of Computer Manuals
- IBM Program Product, 1971-1981; 1971 1981; 10.03 linear feet; 20 archival boxes and 3 archival folders
  - DB/DC Driver System. Specifications, Nov 1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Development Management System/Customer Information Control System/Virtual Storage: Application Program Design Guide, Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Development Management System/Customer Information Control System/Virtual Storage: Operations Guide, Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Development Management System/Customer Information Control System/Virtual Storage: Program Reference Manual, Oct 1979 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Development Management System/CICS/VS, Release 2.0. Specifications, Nov 1979 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Development Management System/Distributed Processing Control Executive: General Information Manual, Nov 1979 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Development Management System/Distributed Processing Control Executive: Program Reference and Operations Manual, Nov 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Display Management System/3790 (DMS/3790): General Information Manual, Jun 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Display Management System/3790 (DMS/3790): Operations Guide, Feb 1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Display Management System/3790 (DMS/3790): Program Reference Manual, May 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Display Management System/Virtual Storage Version 1 (DMS/VS) General Information Manual, Nov 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Distributed Processing Control Executive. Host Prep: Messages, Sep 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Distributed Processing Control Executive. Programming Guide to Host Communication for System Programmers, Sep 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Document Composition Facility: User's Guide, Apr 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Document Composition Facility and Document Library Facility General Information, Sep 1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - DOS/VS Sort/Merge Version 2. Installation Reference Manual, Jan 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - DOS/VS Sort/Merge Version 2. Programmer's Guide, Nov 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - DOS/VS Sort/Merge Version 2. Programmer's Guide, Jan 1981 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - FASTER Language Facility for the Customer Information Control System (CICS/VS) General Information Manual, Aug 1974 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - FORTRAN Interactive Debug for OS (TSO) and VM/370 (CMS). Design Objectives, Jul 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - FORTRAN IV (G1) Processor for OS and VM/370 (CMS). Specifications, Nov 1972 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - FORTRAN IV (H Extended) Compiler for OS and VM/370 (CMS). Specifications, Nov 1972 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - FORTRAN IV Library (Mod I) for OS and VM/370 (CMS). Specifications, Nov 1972 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - FORTRAN IV Library (Mod II) for OS and VM/370 (CMS). Specifications, Nov 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Generalized Information System/Virtual Storage (GIS/VS). General Information Manual, Jan 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Host Prep: Guide to Host Services, Sep 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Host Prep: Interactive Program Validation Services User's Guide, Sep 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Host Prep: Subsystem Information Retrieval Facility Guide and Reference, Sep 1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Host Prep Programming: Statements Reference, Sep 1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Configurator, Jun 1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Diagnosis: Guide, Sep 1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. General Information: Concepts, Sep 1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. General Information: Introduction, Mar 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Host Support Programming: Statements Reference, Mar 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Installation, Nov 1980 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Library User's Guide: Topical Index and Glossary, Oct 1980 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Messages, Sep 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Operations: Basic Mode, Sep 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Operations: Command Mode, Mar 1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Planning, Sep 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Programming: Guide to Data Set Management, Sep 1980 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Programming: Guide to Program Structure, Sep 1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Programming: Guide to Terminals and Printers, Mar 1980 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Terminal Operations: Display Stations, Sep 1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Control Executive. Terminal Operations: Program Executive Monitor Guide, Sep 1980 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Systems Executive Release 2.2: General Information Manual, Jun 1980 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Systems Executive Release 2.2: Installation Guide, Jun 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Systems Executive Release 2.2: Program Reference and Operations Manual, Jun 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Host Command Facility User's Guide. VTAM and Advanced Communications Function for VTAM, Mar 1980 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Host Command Facility User's Guide. TCAM and Advanced Communications Function for TCAM, Mar 1980 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - IBM CMS User's Guide for COBOL, Jan 1981 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Compiler and Library Installation Reference Material, May 1981 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Compiler and Library Programmer's Guide, May 1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Compiler Program Logic, Sep 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Compiler Program Logic, Nov 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Compiler Program Logic. Release 3 (1 of 2), May 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Compiler Program Logic. Release 3 (2 of 2), May 1981 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Subroutine Library Program Logic, Mar 1974 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Subroutine Library Program Logic, Aug 1975 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Subroutine Library Program Logic, Dec 1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Subroutine Library Program Logic, Aug 1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - IBM DOS/VS COBOL Subroutine Library Program Logic, May 1981 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - IBM FORTRAN Program Products for OS and the CMS Component of VM/370 General Information, Apr 1974 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - IBM OS COBOL Interactive Debug and (TSO) COBOL Prompter General Information, May 1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - IBM OS FORTRAN IV (H Extended) Compiler Programmer's Guide, Jun 1972 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - IBM OS Full American National Standard COBOL Compiler and Library, Version 4, Programmer's Guide, Jul 1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - IBM System/360 OS FORTRAN IV (H Extended) Compiler and Library (Mod II) Messages, Mar 1971 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - IBM System/360 OS FORTRAN IV (H Extended) Compiler Program Logic (1 of 2), Mar 1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - IBM System/360 OS FORTRAN IV (H Extended) Compiler Program Logic (2 of 2), Mar 1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - IBM System/360 OS FORTRAN IV Library (Mod II) Program Logic Manual, Mar 1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - IBM System/370 Planning, Control, and Decision Evaluation System/Interactive. Operations Guide, Oct 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - IBM System/370 Planning, Control, and Decision Evaluation System/Interactive. (PLANCODE/I), Jul 1977-Aug 1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - IBM System/370 Planning, Control, and Decision Evaluation System/Interactive. Program Reference Manual, Aug 1979 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - IBM System/370 Planning, Control, and Decision Evaluation System. (PLANCODE) General Information Manual, May 1979 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - IBM Virtual Machine Facility/370 Basic System Extensions General Information Manual, Apr 1978 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - IBM Virtual Machine/System Product: VM/Pass-Through Facility. General Information, Sep 1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - IBM VM/370 (CMS) Terminal User's Guide for FORTRAN IV Program Products, Apr 1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - IBM VM/370 Terminal User's Guide for FORTRAN IV Program Products, Mar 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - IBM VM/370 (CMS) Terminal User's Guide for FORTRAN IV Program Products, May 1977 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - IBM VM/370 CMS User's Guide for COBOL, Dec 1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - IMS/VS Automated Operator Facility (AOF). General Information Manual, Feb 1979 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Application Programming: Designing and Coding, Jul 1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Fast Path Feature. General Information Manual, Apr 1978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. General Information Manual, Jul 1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Installation Guide, Sep 1978 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Master Index and Glossary, Dec 1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Messages and Codes Reference Manual, May 1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Message Format Service User's Guide, Oct 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Operator's Reference Manual, Sep 1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Operator's Reference Manual, Mar 1979 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Primer, Sep 1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Release 1.5. Specifications, Mar 1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. System Programming Reference Manual, Oct 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Utilities Reference Manual (1 of 2), Sep 1978 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - IMS/VS Version 1. Utilities Reference Manual (2 of 2), Sep 1978 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Information Management System/360, Version 2. General Information Manual, Jun 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Information Management System/Virtual Storage (IMS/VS). System/Application Design Guide, Apr 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Information Management System/Virtual Storage (IMS/VS). System/Application Design Guide, Jul 1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Information/System: Program Description and Operations Manual, Jan 1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Installing Host Prep for use with DOS/VS, Sep 1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Interactive Productivity Facility: VSE Feature Reference Manual, Release 4.0, Sep 1981 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Introduction to Advanced Communications Function, May 1979 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - MVS/System Extensions, Undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Network Communications Control Facility. General Information, Jun 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Network Operation Support Program General Information, Jul 1977 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Network Problem Determination Application General Information, Oct 1978 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - OS Assembler H Logic, Sep 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - OS Sort/Merge. General Information, Apr 1973 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - OS Sort/Merge. Programmer's Guide, Mar 1973 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - OS Sort/Merge. Programmer's Guide, Dec 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - OS/VS Sort/Merge. General Information, Feb 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - OS/VS Sort/Merge. Installation Reference Manual, Mar 1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - OS/VS Sort/Merge. Programmer's Guide, Sep 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - OS/VS1 and OS/VS2 MVS. Programmed Cryptographic Facility. General Information Manual, May 1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - OS/VS2 MVS Hierarchical Storage Manager. Messages, Sep 1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - OS/VS2 MVS Hierarchical Storage Manager System. Programmer's Reference and Operations Guide, Nov 1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - OS/VS2 MVS Hierarchical Storage Manager. User's Guide, Nov 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - OS/VS2 MVS Resource Access Control Facility (RACF). General Information Manual, May 1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - OS/VS2 MVS Resource Measurement Facility (RMF). Reference and User's Guide, Jul 1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - OS/VS2 MVS Resource Measurement Facility (RMF) Version 2. General Information Manual, May 1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - OS/VS2 MVS/System Extensions Release 2. General Information Manual, May 1979 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - OS/VS2 MVS/System Product. General Information Manual, Aug 1980 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - OS/VS2 MVS TSO 3270 Extended Display Support - Session Manager User's Guide and Reference, Jul 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - OS/VS2 MVS TSO Command Package: User's Guide and Reference, May 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Planning Systems Generator II (PSG II). General Information, Dec 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Planning Systems Generator II (PSG II). Operations Guide, Jun 1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Program Systems Generator II (PSG II). Specifications, Nov 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Project Management System IV (PMS IV). Cost Processor Program Description and Operations Manual, Feb 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Project Management System IV (PMS IV). Extended Network Processor Program Description and Operations Manual, Jan 1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Project Management System IV (PMS IV). Resource Allocation Processor Program Description and Operations Manual, Feb 1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Structured Programming Facility/Conversational Monitor System: General Information Manual, Sep 1979 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - System Productivity Facility for MVS. General Information, Aug 1980 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Teleprocessing Network Simulator Release 5.0: General Information Manual, Sep 1979 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Time Sharing Option 3270 Display Support and Structured Programming Facility Version 2.2: General Information Manual, Jul 1979 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - VIDEO/370 Including the CICS Feature. General Information, Apr 1974 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - VIDEO/370 Including the CICS Feature. User's Guide, May 1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - VS APL. General Information, Aug 1976 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - VS APL. Installation Reference Material, Jan 1978 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - VS APL for CMS: Terminal User's Guide, Oct 1976 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - VS APL for VSPC: Terminal User's Guide, Oct 1976 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - VS APL for VSPC: Terminal User's Guide, Apr 1977 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - VS BASIC. General Information, Oct 1976 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - VS BASIC. Installation Reference Material, Sep 1976 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - VS BASIC. Installation Reference Material, Dec 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - VS BASIC. OS/VS and DOS/VS Programmer's Guide, Dec 1976 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - VS BASIC CMS. Terminal User's Guide, Dec 1976 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - VS BASIC for VSPC: Terminal User's Guide, Dec 1976 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions Diagnosis Reference: Error Recovery and Recording Transients, Oct 1979 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions Diagnosis Reference: Initial Program Load and Job Control, Oct 1979 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions Diagnosis Reference: Linkage Editor, Oct 1979 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions Diagnosis Reference: Linkage Editor, Jul 1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions Diagnosis Reference: Maintain System History Program, Jul 1980 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions Diagnosis Reference: Serviceability Aids Release 2, Oct 1979 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions Diagnosis Reference: Serviceability Aids Release 3, Jul 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions. Maintain System History Program. User's Guide, Jul 1980 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions. Support for IBM 3375, May 1981 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - VSE/Advanced Functions. System Generation, Jul 1980 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Installation and Operations Reference, Dec 1979 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Installation and Operations Reference, Jul 1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Logic, Volume I, Dec 1979 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Logic, Volume II (1 of 2), Jun 1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Logic, Volume II (2 of 2), Jun 1979 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Messages, Dec 1979 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Messages, Sep 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Terminal User's Guide, Dec 1979 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - VSE/Interactive Computing and Control Facility. Terminal User's Guide, Sep 1980 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - VSE/Interactive Problem Control System: Logic, Nov 1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - VSE/Interactive Problem Control System: Logic, Aug 1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - VSE/Interactive Problem Control System. User's Guide and Reference, Nov 1979 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - VSE/VSAM Messages and Codes, Feb 1979 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - VSE/VSAM Programmer's Reference, Feb 1979 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- IBM Student Text, 1962-1978; 0.03 linear feet; 3 archival folders
  The IBM Student Texts series contains computer manuals underneath that heading.The Student Texts series contains computer manuals underneath that heading.
  - Introduction to IBM Data Processing Systems, Jul 1978 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - A Programmer's Introduction to IBM System/360 Assembler Language, Sep 1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Programming the IBM 1440 Data Processing System, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- IBM Systems, 1972-1981; 10 linear feet
  The IBM Systems series contains computer manuals underneath that heading.
  - ACF/TAP User's Guide (Advanced Communications Function/Trace Analysis Program), Sep 1977 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Advanced Communications Function for VTAM (ACF/VTAM). Program Operator Guide, Jul 1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Advanced Function for Communications System Summary, Jul 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - APL Language, Feb 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Data Security Through Cryptography, Oct 1977 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Device Support Facilities 3.0, Jan 1981 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Distributed Processing Control Executive/3790. Host Support: Host Services Guide, Aug 1979 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Distributed Processing Control Executive/3790. Host Support: Messages, Aug 1979 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Distributed Processing Control Executive/3790. Host Support: Subsystem Information Retrieval Facility Guide and Reference, Mar 1980 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - DOS to OS/MFT, OS/MVT, OS/VS1. Management Planning Guide, Aug 1972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - DOS/VS Access Method Services. User's Guide, Apr 1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - DOS/VS Data Management Guide, Mar 1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - DOS/VS Messages, Apr 1977 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - DOS/VS to OS/VS1 Implementation Guide, Jun 1977 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - DOS/VS Supervisor and I/O Macros, Apr 1977 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - DOS/VSE Macro User's Guide, Feb 1979 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - DOS/VSE System Utilities, Feb 1979 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Recording Editing and Printing (EREP) Program, Jun 1980 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - A Guide to the IBM 3031 Processor Complex and Attached Processor Complex of System/370, Apr 1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Guide to Using the IBM 3704 Communications Controller Control Panel, Sep 1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Guide to Using the IBM 3705 Communications Controller Control Panel, May 1979 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - IBM 3031 Processor Complex and 3031 Attached Processor Complex Functional Characteristics, Dec 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - IBM 3031 Processor Complex Operator's Guide, Jan 1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - IBM 3262 Printer Models 3 and 13 Component Description, Dec 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - IBM 3262 Printer Models 2 and 12 Component Description, Feb 1980 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - IBM 3270 Information Display System. 3274 Control Unit Model 5/C Description, Configuration and Physical Planning, Sep 1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - IBM 3270 Information Display System. 3274 Control Unit Operator's Guide, Apr 1980 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - IBM 3270 Information Display System. 3278 Display Station Operator's Guide, Jul 1979 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - IBM 3270 Information Display System. Description and Configuration, May 1979 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - IBM 3287 Printer Models 1 and 2 Component Description, Feb 1980 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - IBM 3287 Printer Models 1 and 2 Operator's Guide for Rear Document Insertion Device, Apr 1980 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - IBM 3287 Printer Models 1C and 2C Component Description, Dec 1979 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - IBM 3287 Printer Operator's Guide, Oct 1977 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - IBM 3704 and 3705 Communications Controllers Assembler Language, May 1975 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - IBM 3704 and 3705 Communications Controllers Assemblers Language, May 1979 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - IBM 3704 and 3705 Communications Controllers. Network Control Program Generation and Utilities. Guide and Reference Manual (for OS/MFT and OS/MVT TCAM Users), Aug 1973 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - IBM 3704 and 3705 Communications Controllers. Principles of Operation, May 1979 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - IBM 3704 and 3705 Emulation Program. Generation and Utilities. Guide and Reference Manual, May 1976 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - IBM 3790 Communication System. Programming Statements Guide, Sep 1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - IBM 3790 Communication System. Programming Statements Reference, Aug 1978 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - IBM 3803 Model 1, IBM 3420 Models 3, 5 and 7 Magneitc Tape Subsystems. Component Description, May 1973 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - IBM 3803 Model 2, IBM 3420 Models 4, 6 and 8 Magnetic Tape Subsystems. Subsystem Description, Mar 1974 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - IBM 4300 Processors. Principles of Operation for EXPS: VSE Mode, Jan 1979 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. 8101 Storage and Input/Output Unit Description, Jan 1980 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Bibliography, Dec 1980 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Communications Attachment Manual, Feb 1980 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Communications, Loop and Display/Printer. Attachment Description, Jan 1980 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Direct Access Storage Devices Description, May 1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Distributed Processing Programming Executive. Library User's Guide, Apr 1980 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Principles of Operation, Jan 1980 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Problem Management Guide, Sep 1980 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - IBM 8100 Information System. Site Planning and Preparation Guide for IBM 8101, IBM 8130, IBM 8140, Jun 1980 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - IBM 8130 and 8140 Processors. Operator's Guide, Nov 1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - IBM 8140 Processor Description, Jun 1980 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - IBM 8775 Display Terminal. Character Set Reference, Sep 1979 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - IBM 8775 Display Terminal. Component Description, Mar 1980 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - IBM 8775 Display Terminal. Configuration, Jul 1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - IBM 8775 Display Terminal. Site Preparation Guide, Nov 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - IBM 8775 Display Terminal. Terminal User's Guide, Apr 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - IBM Cryptographic Subsystem. Concepts and Facilities, Nov 1979-Feb1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - IBM Multiuse Communications Loop. Installation Guide, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)